# Morgan Stanley

Farmington, UT 84025 | 801-726-6508 | morganpstanley@gmail.com Github | Website | LinkedIn

#### JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript-based programming with a strong background in design and typography. Focused on team-driven results with an emphasis on good communication. Enjoy problem-solving and understanding systems. Continuously seek improvement through feedback.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Javascript, React, Ruby, Rails, SQL, HTML, CSS, Adobe Illustrator

## **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

Stocker - Github

React + Redux | Ruby on Rails | HTML + CSS

An app that tracks user-selected stocks in real-time.

- Connected to Finnhub Stock API and uses a Websocket to keep stock prices up-to-date
- Allows users to input a buy price to track the gain/loss of their investments and their portfolio as a whole

Pro Lift - Github

JavaScript | Ruby on Rails | HTML + CSS

Allows users to log and track workout data, watch exercise technique videos, and look at what days of the current month they've worked out.

Uses Date() to create a calendar and highlight the current date and any date that matches a logged workout.

Movie Database - Github Ruby on Rails | HTML

Allows users to organize lists of movies and view other's users' lists.

- Uses ActiveRecord relations and SQLite to save and store user-inputted data and relationships
- Uses OAuth verification to allow users to log in through Github and bcrypt gem to encrypt user data

## **EXPERIENCE**

Bountiful, UT **Costco Wholesale** 

Stocker May 2015 - June 2019

- Made sure items on the floor were well-stocked and organized. Was often asked to take charge when reorganizing items on the floor to create a cohesive and natural flow to lead members to what they were looking for as well as our focus items. Management was comfortable leaving me in charge of a key area for several months after my boss was
- Bountiful Costco Employee of the Month April 2016

FedEx Ground Salt Lake City, UT June 2014 - August 2016

Load Coach/Package Handler Trainer

 Supervised and trained package handlers to efficiently and safely carry out their responsibilities. Oversaw eight-12 package handlers and over 1200 packages an hour packaged safely in trailers. Our side was constantly ranked in top one-two out of 16 in hub for overall performance.

• SLC North Hub Employee of the Month - June 2015

Package Handler

May 2012 - June 2014

- Loaded trailers with packages quickly and efficiently. Averaged between 380-420 boxes/hour. Loaded trailers 15-20% faster and 2-5% fuller than average trailer, which resulted in decrease in damaged boxes due to overflowing trailers. Resulting work was often displayed to new hires as an example good loading technique.
- SLC North Hub Employee of the Month Dec 2014

## **EDUCATION**

Flatiron School Farmington, Utah June 2019 - August 2020

Online Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

Ogden, Utah

Weber State University Completed 74 credits towards Bachelors of Business Administration

Recipient of Weber State University Emerging Leader Scholarship

Member of Weber State University Honors Program - completed 15 credits in honors courses